本:你很帅,爸爸.
Ben: Looking sharp dad.
杰森:我也没办法.
Jason: Well I have no choice.
看你妈妈,一个需要特别照顾的女人,
See your mother, a women in the high maintenance category,
非要过个高档的晚上.
requires a top drawer evening.
本:要我说,爸爸,那就是一个大热天里的虾味爆米花之夜.
Ben: F.Y.I.dad, its popcorn-shrimp night at the sizzler.
杰森:可惜三个月前我们打算的是看戏,晚餐,
Jason: Well thanks but unfortunately three months ago we planned tonight
跳舞,什么的.
for a special night of theater, dinner, dancing, and the works.
本:什么的?啊,你是说那个.
Ben: The works?Ah, you mean sex.
杰森:本,我知道你15岁了,但不是你听到的每一件事都是那个的意思.
Jason: Ben I know your 15 but not everything you hear is a euphemism for sex.
本:是啊,我知道.
Ben: Well I guess not.
我是说你好像不太喜欢约妈妈出去.
I mean you sure don't seem very excited about taking mom out.
杰森:那是因为我要准备星期一的演讲,
Jason: Well it's just that I have a speech to prepare for Monday,
还有下周诊所的预算.
I've got the clinic budgets due next week,
我本想取消今晚的约会,但那会伤透你妈妈的心.
and I'd cancel tonight but it would break your mother's heart.
噢,你太漂亮了.
Oh, you look fabulous.
麦琪:几个月来我一直盼望着这一天呢.
Maggie: Well I have been looking forward to this for months.
杰森:我去发动汽车.我太激动了.
Jason: I'll pull the car around.I'm thrilled!
麦琪:噢,我也是.我本来一点也不想去的.
Maggie: Oh, me too!Ah...I'd do anything to get out of this.
本:什么?
Ben: Huh?
麦琪:噢,
Maggie: Oh, I've got a column due next week,
下周要交一篇稿子,而且我还在写另一篇.
and I'm in the middle of researching another.
出去一晚对我简直是火上浇油.
I need a night out like I need a paper cut.
本:哦,妈妈,你知道,如果你不去爸爸肯定会很失望的.
Ben: Gee mom, you know, dad sure would be disappointed if you didn't go.
麦琪:噢,我知道,但是…
Maggie: Oh, I know, but...
开萝尔:妈妈,我能借用你的香水吗?
Carol: Mom is it ok if I borrowed your perfume?
麦琪:噢,当然,
Maggie: Oh, of course honey!
亲爱的!随便用,你能回家我太高兴了.
Anything you want, I'm just so glad to have you home.
开萝尔:妈妈,放松点,你快把我的骨头勒断了.
Carol: Mom, take it easy your giving me hug burns.
本:听,妈妈,爸爸都等不及了.
Ben: Man, dad can't wait to get you alone mom.
开萝尔:我绝不会要这样的婚姻.噢,
Carol: Marriage is never going to do that to me.
凯特,谢谢你同意跟德怀特和我共进晚餐.
Oh Kate, thanks for agreeing to have diner with Dwight and me.
我是说我真希望迈克和德怀特能成为朋友.
I mean I really want Mike and Dwight to be friends but I know you had
但我知道迈克今晚能来是你劝说的.
to talk Mike into coming tonight.
凯特:别傻了,是迈克自己想来的.他高兴极了.
Kate: Don't be silly, Mike is really looking forward to this.He is so excited.
迈克:我肚子里生蛔虫了.
Mike: I've got a tape worm.
开萝尔:小可怜!哪里疼?
Carol: Poor baby!Where does it hurt?
迈克:啊,对,对,就是那.
Mike: Ah, well, well right there.
开萝尔:你快去吧,如果你伤了德怀特的心,
Carol: You're going, and if you hurt Dwight's feelings you'll wish you
那你肯定会生蛔虫的.
had a tape worm.
迈克:噢,天哪!伦敦之旅真的让她成熟了.
Mike: Oh my!A trip to London really mellowed her out.
凯特:蛔虫?
Kate: A tape worm?
迈克:我本想说软骨病来着,
Mike: Well I was going to go with rickets,
但我估计她不会再上当了.
but I figured she wouldn't buy it two times in a row.
克莉丝:为什么你们不告诉妈妈爸爸不想去?
Chrissy: Why didn't you tell mommy that daddy didn't really want to go?
本:啊,因为他们以为我要复习化学.
Ben: Well, because they think I'm going over to Stinky's.
克莉丝:所以?
Chrissy: So?
本:啊,实际上我要和查克·斯泰克出去兜风.
Ben: Well, I'm actually going cruising with Chuck Stake.
今晚他会让我坐在车里.
Tonight he's going to let me ride inside the car.
克莉丝:你撒谎.
Chrissy: You told a lie!
本:安静点,否则我烧了你的去迪斯尼的录像带.
Ben: Quiet or I'll melt your Disney tapes.(Talking on the phone) Hello.
(讲电话)喂,是那个今晚要忍受你的女人.
It's the woman who has to put up with you tonight.
腿伤了?不能来照顾孩子了?
A broken leg?As in you can't come baby-sit?
如果骨头没露出来,我看不出有什么理由不来.但是你该来.
Well, if no bones are poking out, I don't see why not?But you have to!
这事关生死.啊!
It's a matter of life and death!Ah!
本:我不信.我是要去和查克·斯泰克兜风的.
Ben: I don't believe this.I was actually going to ride with Chuck Stake.
不在旁边跑.不再解释为什么我需要新鞋.
No more running along side.No more explaining why I need new shoes.
克莉丝:嘘…我在看电视呢.
Chrissy: Shh...I'm watching TV.
本:是你啊,查克·斯泰克!进来吗?
Ben: Yo, Chuck Stake!You want to come in?
克莉丝:我们在看呢.你看起来像个失败者.
Chrissy: We are watching the Little Mermaid.You looked like a loser.
德怀特:欢迎来到被时间遗忘的地方.
Dwight: Welcome to the land that time forgot.
迈克:这是阁楼吧.
Mike: It's an attic.
开萝尔:不,不是的.这是一个中世纪风格的宴会厅.
Carol: Not its not!It's a Mid-evil banquette hall.
迈克:啊,那我错了.
Mike: Ah, my mistake.
凯特:开萝尔,一切都那么美.
Kate: Carol everything looks beautiful.
开萝尔:谢谢.那么,请坐,别拘束.
Carol: Why thank you.Now, please sit down and make yourselves comfortable.
德怀特:我去取我们盛大的晚餐,
Dwight: I'll go fetch our sumptuous repasts,
然后我们就可以饥餐渴饮饱餐一顿了.
so we can slay our appetites and slake our thirsts.
开萝尔:你是说你们这就要开始吃喝了.需要我帮忙吗,
Carol: That means you get to eat and drink.
我最最亲爱的?
Do you need some help my dearest darling?
德怀特:噢,不.谢谢你,我美味的小羊排.
Dwight: Oh, no thank you my luscious lamb-chop.
开萝尔:你肯定吗,我强壮的搬运工.
Carol: Are you sure my stalwart stevedore?
德怀特:相当肯定,我反复无常的村姑.
Dwight: Quite, my whimsical wench.
迈克:去拿吃的.
Mike: Get the food!
凯特:开萝尔,你的裙子真漂亮.
Kate: Carol, your dress is beautiful.
开萝尔:谢谢,这是德怀特做的.是的,他缝的.
Carol: Thank you, Dwight made it.Yes, he sews.
迈克:德怀特,你是怎么打开那扇门的?
Mike: Dwight, how did you open that door?
德怀特:噢,很简单.我在门两边都装了电压垫,所以门就可以自动开关了.
Dwight: Oh, it's simple.I rigged it to electric pressure mats on both sides, so the door opens and closes on its own.
迈克:你哪来的主意,达芬奇丢失的笔记里?
Mike: Where did you get that idea, the lost note books of Leonardo da Vinci?
德怀特:不,是提醒了我.
Dwight: No, the door of the Piggly-Wiggly.
杰森:(自言自语)我可以增加诊所的人力.你不该这么想,
Jason: (thinking to himself) I could increase clinic manpower.
你应该和妻子享受一晚.
Will you knock it off; you suppose to be enjoying a night out with your wife.
噢,看看她,从来没有这么高兴过.
Oh, look at her, having the time of her life.
麦琪:(自言自语)我给你钱掉转车头吧.
Maggie: (thinking to herself) I'd give you cash to turn this car around.
不行;你知道他多么想要今晚的约会.
Stop it; you know how much he wants to go out tonight.
杰森:我本该做家务.我应该告诉她.
Jason: I'd rather put thumb tacks in my shorts.I should tell her.
麦琪:家里要做的事情太多了;我一定得告诉他.杰森…
Maggie: I've got so much to do at home; I've got to tell him.Jason....
杰森:宝贝,我…你先说.
Jason: Sweetheart I've...You go first.
麦琪:亲爱的,你觉得今晚出来怎么样?
Maggie: Honey, how do you feel about going out tonight?
杰森,噢,令人激动,兴奋.你呢?
Jason: Oh, jazzed and tingly.You?
麦琪:噢,激动差不多.只有一点兴奋.
Maggie: Oh, in the ballpark of jazzed.Just a side of tingly.
杰森:什么,更像是,呃…
Jason: What, more like, uhhh...
麦琪:我得回去做家务.
Maggie: I'd rather have thumb tacks in my shorts.
杰森:我也是.
Jason: Me too.
麦琪:亲爱的,很抱歉…你也要做家务吗?
Maggie: Honey, I'm so sorry...you'd rather have thumb tacks too?
杰森:是的,今晚我不想出去了.你想回家吗?
Jason: Yeah, I don't want to go out tonight.You want to go home?
麦琪:噢,你说对了.噢,亲爱的,这是我们做过的最傻的事了吧?
Maggie: Oh you bet.Oh honey, isn't this the silliest thing we have ever done?
杰森:我们确实有点小误会,
Jason: Well we did have a slight miscommunication,
但是在互相深爱的基础上.
based on our great love for one another.
现在我们可以在下一个斜坡下车.径直回家,利用好今晚剩下的时间.
Here we can stop next ramp straight home make the most what is left this evening.
麦琪:好吧,可我们怎么慢下来了?
Maggie: Ok, but why are we slowing down?
杰森:前面的刹车灯亮了.可能只是耽误一小会.
Jason: Well, there's brake lights up ahead.Probably just some minor delay.
凯特:这萝卜汤…呃…挺有意思.
Kate: This turnip soup is...umm...it's interesting.
迈克:百分之九十九没味.
Mike: Ninety-nine percent flavor free.
开萝尔:你一点冒险精神也没有.
Carol: You have absolutely no since of adventure.
迈克:嘿,我来了,不是吗?
Mike: Hey, I'm here aren't I?
凯特:那么,呃,德怀特,我们还有什么吃的?
Kate: So, uh, Dwight what else are we having?
德怀特:本以为你们不会问呢.瞧.
Dwight: Thought you'd never ask.Voila.
凯特:肉?
Kate: Meat?
开萝尔:德怀特,我想我告诉你了,凯特不吃有脸的东西.
Carol: Dwight, I thought I told you, Kate doesn't eat anything with a face.
德怀特:我把它切下来.
Dwight: I cut it off.
迈克:只是出于好奇.德怀特,有脸的时候它是什么样的?
Mike: Well, just out of curiosity Dwight, what was it when it had a face?
德怀特:就像你们花园里普通的麝鼠.
Dwight: Just your plain, garden variety muskrat.
迈克:麝鼠?德怀特,
Mike: Muskrat?Dwight, where did you get a muskrat?
你从哪弄的麝鼠?是不是什么花园里的人来找你了,
Did some guy in an alley come up to you, open his coat,
打开外套,它就挂在那呢?
and it was just hanging there?
德怀特:你认识莫尔夫吗?
Dwight: You know Merve?
迈克:开萝尔,你从前有过几个古怪的男朋友,但这回你可创记录了.
Mike: Carol, you've had some weird boyfriends before but this time you got the door prize.
开萝尔:好吧,迈克,行了.向德怀特道歉,否则我就再也不理你了.
Carol: Ok Mike, that it, apologize to Dwight or I am never talking to you again?
迈克:好极了!一石二鸟.
Mike: Great!Two birds with one stone.
德怀特:你有过其他男朋友?
Dwight: You've had other boyfriends?
开萝尔:啊,我该料到的.我是说我们不可能成为朋友.
Carol: Ah, I should have known.I mean there is no way for us to be friends.
我们就像油和水,聪明和愚蠢.
We are like oil and water, smart and stupid,
德怀特,我告诉过你凯特是素食者.
and Dwight I told you Kate was a vegetarian.
凯特:开萝尔,他是好意.
Kate: Carol, he meant well.
德怀特:嘿,我能管好自己的女人.
Dwight: Hey, I can handle my own woman.
凯特:自己的女人?开萝尔,你们是那种关系吗?
Kate: Your own woman?Carol, is that the kind of relationship you two have?
开萝尔:你跟我谈关系的事,你说他?
Carol: You're talking to me about relationships and you're with that?
迈克:噢,嘿,
Mike: Oh, hey, let's face facts here.
让我们面对现实吧.
There are four people in this room; two of them are wearing tights,
房间里有四个人;其中两个已经闹翻了,幸好不是我们.
and it isn't us.
凯特,来吧,收拾东西我们离开这.
Kate, come on get your stuff, we are out of here.
凯特:德怀特,我们过得很开心.
Kate: Dwight we had a lovely time.
迈克:不,不,不.
Mike: No, no, no.
凯特,你不必客气,除非你想被请回去.
Kate you don't have to be polite unless you want to be invited back.
德怀特:嘿!
Dwight: Hey!
本:嘿!
Ben: Hey!
克莉丝:嘿!发生什么事了?
Chrissy: Hey!What happened?
本:灯灭了.
Ben: The lights went off.
克莉丝:谢谢你,科学先生.把灯打开吧.
Chrissy: Thank you Mr.Science.Now put them back on.
本:克莉丝,我不能.我想停电了.
Ben: Chrissy I can't, I think the power is off.
克莉丝:我不喜欢黑暗.
Chrissy: I don't like the dark.
本:噢,这有些火柴.克莉丝,放开我的腿.
Ben: Oh, here's some matches.Chrissy get off my leg.
克莉丝:好的.
Chrissy: Ok.
本:噢!这下好多了.我去看看到底怎么回事.抓住.别那么紧!天啊,整个街区都黑了.
Ben: Aw!!Oh, that's lots better.I'm going to see if I can find out
what happened.Hold on.Not that tight!Man, the whole neighborhood is dark
克莉丝:你干什么了?
Chrissy: What did you do?
本:什么也没干!是停电,怎么能怪我呢?
Ben: Nothing!It's a power failure, why are you blaming me?
克莉丝:妈妈爸爸在家时从没发生多这样的事.
Chrissy: This never happens when mommy or daddy are home.
本:看,你就呆在这,
Ben: Look, you stay right here, I know where a flashlight is.
我知道哪有手电.妈妈总是把他放在…呃…圣诞装饰旁边.
Mom keeps it up here next to the uh....Christmas ornaments.
太好了,还能用.
Great, it still works.
克莉丝:那不是真灯.把真灯打开.
Chrissy: That's not a real light.Put the lamp back on.
本:克莉丝,不行.没有电.
Ben: Chrissy, I can't there is no electricity.
克莉丝:噢,那我们就看电视等电来吧.
Chrissy: Oh, so let's watch television tell it comes back on.
本:下次我再照顾你,爸爸就得给我买辆车.
Ben: Next time I baby-sit you, dad is buying me a car.
太棒了,有收音机.现在也许我们可以知道发生什么事了.
Great, here is the radio.Now maybe we can find out what is going on.
克莉丝:等等,我不能看电视,但你却能听收音机?
Chrissy: Wait a minute, I can't watch T.V.but you can listen to the radio?
本:克莉丝!我们来玩个叫"闭嘴"的游戏.你先来.
Ben: Chrissy!We are going to play a little game called "shut up".You go first.
收音机播音员:暴风刮落了很多电线,造成长岛大部分地区停电.
Radio announcer: The storm has downed a number of power lines causing blackouts over most of long island.
收音机播音员:当局预计停电可能还要持续八到十二个小时.
Radio announcer: Local predicts that the blackout will last another eight to twelve hours.
迈克:一个小中断,好吧!德怀特,开门.
Mike: A blackout, great!Dwight, open the door.
德怀特:噢!
Dwight: Woops!
迈克:我不想听这家伙说'噢'.
Mike: I don't want to hear woops from this guy.
德怀特:我刚刚想起门的电是和房子的主电线连在一起的.
Dwight: I just remembered that the door is electrically patched into the
我们无法期望这个时代的房子…
main circuitry of the house.No way can we date a house of this age....
迈克:有话直说.
Mike: Cut to the chase.
德怀特:我们就向老鼠一样被困住了.
Dwight: We are trapped like rats.
迈克:好吧.凯特,注意点,我打破窗子了.
Mike: All right.Kate, watch you, I am going to break a window.
凯特:迈克!
Kate: Mike!
开萝尔:等等,等等!
Carol: Wait, wait, wait!There is an icy wind out there and the heat is off.
外面寒风刺骨,又没有暖气.你什么也别打破.
You are not breaking anything.
迈克:看,开萝尔.我要做的就是找点什么贴上字条说明我们的情况,再把他扔到街上去.
Mike: Look Carol, all I have to do is throw something down to the street with a note attached explaining our situation.
那么,呃,我们能找到什么最不值钱的东西?
Now, uh, what's the most worthless thing we've got up here?
开萝尔:离我的德怀特远点.
Carol: You leave my Dwight alone.
凯特:这开始变冷了.
Kate: It's getting cold.
德怀特:别以为我会被冻死.我一直以为那会是在洗澡的时候.
Dwight: Never thought I'd die by freezing.I always thought it would be a shower mishap.
迈克:来吧,我们不会被冻着的.有很多方法可以保暖.比如,呃…
Mike: Come on, we are not going to freeze.There are plenty of ways to keep warm.Like, uh...
德怀特:我们可以吃东西.
Dwight: We could eat.
开萝尔/迈克/凯特:传递
Carol/Mike/Kate: Pass
德怀特:我是说甜点.
Dwight: I was talking about dessert.
迈克:噢,别告诉我.是莫尔夫买给你的那只鹅做的鹅肉浆果馅饼吗?
Mike: Oh, don't tell me.Merve sold you a goose for a goose berry pie?
德怀特:不,是华夫甜饼.
Dwight: No, waffle sweet-cake.
凯特:我快饿死了.你保证这里一点肉也没有?
Kate: I'm starved.Promise there is not a speck of meat in this?
德怀特:一点也没有.只用了猪头样的一瓶酒.
Dwight: None.Just a hogs heard of "wassa wine".
杰森:让让,傻瓜.
Jason: Move it goober.
麦琪:感觉好点了吗?
Maggie: Feel better?
杰森:是的,直到我发现有辆警车在我们前面.
Jason: I did until I realized that is a police car in front of us.
警察:请原谅,先生.你刚才是叫我傻瓜吗?
Police man: Excuse me sir, but did you just call me goober?
杰森:我是说警官,警官.谢谢询问.晚安.
Jason: That was trooper, trooper.Thanks for asking.Good night.
警察:前面有一些电线断了.岛上大部分地区已经停电.
Police man: We've got some downed power lines up ahead.
请别着急.
Most of the island is blacked out.Keep your pants on.
麦琪:停电,杰森,孩子们!
Maggie: A black out, Jason the children!
杰森:噢,放松点,亲爱的.克莉丝有保姆看着,其他人也不会有事.迈克可能正在利用它.
Jason: Oh relax sweetheart.Chrissy is with a sitter, the others are fine.Mike is probably taking advantage of it.
麦琪:噢,好极了!偏偏是今晚不在家.
Maggie: Oh great!Of all the nights to be taken away from home.
杰森:那是什么意思.为什么好像是我的错?
Jason: What's that suppose to mean.What like this is my fault?
麦琪,三个月前今晚只是日历上普通的一天.
Maggie, three months ago tonight was just a date on the calendar.
是我们共同把它圈起来作为共同享受生活的时间的.
We mutually circled it for some quality time together.
麦琪:噢,这就是你的想法?
Maggie: Oh, is that all this is to you?
杰森:问题是…
Jason: The point is...
麦琪:这算什么,诊所里看病吗?
Maggie: What is this, some kind of clinical exercise?
好吧,杰森.你的日程表上还有什么?
Ok Jason, what else was on your agenda?
晚上8点说空洞的情话.9点恭维我的耳环.
Eight P.M.say empty romantic words.Nine P.M.compliment my earrings.Eleven P.
11点吻我,然后等着好事?
M.kiss me and hope for the best?
杰森:亲爱的,看,我很抱歉.
Jason: Sweetheart, look I'm sorry.I did want to be with you tonight.
今晚我确实想跟你在一起.我想…等一下,你也不想出来的!!
I wanted to spend...wait a minute, you didn't want to be here either!!
麦琪:不,杰森,我没有说我不想…
Maggie: No Jason, I didn't say I didn't want...
杰森:我绝对没有必要道歉,'
Jason: I have absolutely nothing to apologize for,
今晚不行我有最后期限的工作要做'小姐.
Miss not tonight dear I have a deadline.
麦琪:好吧,如果你非要那么想.
Maggie: Well, if that's the way you feel about it.
杰森:你要去哪?
Jason: Where are you going?
麦琪:我要走回家.至少那有人想和我说话.
Maggie: I am walking home.At least there people want to talk to me.
杰森:啊!
Jason: Ah!
麦琪:外面寒风刺骨,我又穿着薄鞋.
Maggie: There is an icy wind and I am wearing thin shoes.
开萝尔:迈克,开来礼貌小姐受不了她的蛋糕了.
Carol: Well Mike, guess Miss Manners couldn't hold her cake.
迈克:德怀特,一只猪头里到底能装多少酒?
Mike: Dwight, exactly how much wine is in a hogs head?
德怀特:63加仑左右.
Dwight: About sixty-three gallons.
迈克:63加仑?
Mike: Sixty-three gallons?
德怀特:大部分都烧掉了.
Dwight: Most of it cooks off.
迈克:我不信.你先是让我们陷入黑暗,然后给我们吃臭肉,又灌醉了凯特.
Mike: I don't believe this!First you get us trapped in the dark, then you
try to feed us road kill, you get my girl plastered
德怀特:嘿,在洛杉矶人们要为这种晚会花大价钱的.
Dwight: Hey, in LA people pay big buck for a party like that.
迈克:是啊,可这里不是洛杉矶.我们越来越冷了.你打算怎么让我们摆脱麻烦,弯脚趾?
Mike: Yeah well this isn't LA.We are getting colder by the minute.How are you going to get us out of this mess curly, toes?
德怀特:啊,我们可以用帘子遮住说有墙和窗子,阻挡寒气.
Dwight: Well, we can drape every walls, windows, keep out cold.
迈克:好吧,我们到哪找帘子呢?
Mike: Alright, where can we get drapes around here.
开萝尔:是的,他也会做帘子.
Carol: Yes, he does drapes too.
克莉丝:我感觉自己像是果汁软糖人.
Chrissy: I feel like the Stay Puff Marshmallow Man.
为什么不能打开暖气呢?
Why can't we put the heater on?
本:你在抱怨什么?你现在暖和了,不是吗?
Ben: What are you complaining about?Your warm now, aren't you?
克莉丝:是的.
Chrissy: Yes.
本:很好.
Ben: Good.
克莉丝:本?
Chrissy: Ben?
本:什么!?!?
Ben: What!?!?
克莉丝:我要上厕所.
Chrissy: I have to go to the bathroom.
本:什么?你怎么不早说?
Ben: What?Why didn't you say that six layers ago?
克莉丝:因为那时我不想去.
Chrissy: Cause I didn't have to go then.
本:那太不幸了,你只能忍着点了.
Ben: Well too bad, you're just going to have to hold it.
克莉丝:厕所也用电吗?
Chrissy: Is the bathroom electric too?
本:是的!
Ben: Yes!
克莉丝:都是你的错,
Chrissy: This is all your fault Ben Seaver!
本.你弄坏了灯,
You broke the lights, now you broke the bathroom;
现在又弄坏了厕所;我打赌是你搞坏了整个街区.
I bet you broke the whole neighborhood.
本:是啊,克莉丝!
Ben: That's right Chrissy!
一切都是我弄坏的,这些都是我邪恶计划的一部分.
I broke everything, its all part of my sick twisted plan.
你猜怎么样,好戏还在后头呢.我会死掉,外面在结冰,最小的会先死.
Guess what, I saved the best for last.We are going to die, it's freezing outside and the smallest goes first.
克莉丝:(哭)
Chrissy: (cries)
本:噢…好了,克莉丝.我开玩笑的.一切都会好的.
Ben: Aw...come on Chrissy, I'm just kidding.Everything is going to be fine.
克莉丝:不是的.你说的,最小的先死,我就是最小的.
Chrissy: It is not.You said the smallest goes first, and I'm the smallest.
本:看,克莉丝,别哭了.好吧,你想看我做鬼脸吗?
Ben: Look Chrissy don't cry.Ok, you want me to make a "googy" face?
克莉丝:你本来就是鬼脸.
Chrissy: You always have a "googy" face.
本:好吧,我给你讲个故事?三只小猪的故事怎么样?
Ben: Ok, I'll tell you a story?How about the Three Little Pigs?
克莉丝:故事里还有只狼.
Chrissy: There is a wolf in that one.
本:那么…小红帽怎么样?
Ben: Umm...how about Little Red Riding Hood?
克莉丝:那里面也有只狼.
Chrissy: There is a wolf in that one too.
本:面包师呢?
Ben: Ginger Bread Man?
克莉丝:有狼.
Chrissy: Wolf.
本:克莉丝,我做什么事能让你感觉好点吗?
Ben: Chrissy, isn't there anything I can do to make you feel better?
克莉丝:你带我上厕所.
Chrissy: You can take me to the bathroom.
本:说对了.这边走.
Ben: You got it.Walk this way.
抱紧我,宝贝;我会好好照顾你的.
Stick with me cutie-pie; I'll take good care of you.
杰森:五个小时困在车里,一个浪漫的夜晚.啊?
Jason: Five hours stuck in a car that is some romantic evening.What?
麦琪:你在说我们的初次约会?
Maggie: You just described our first date.
杰森:噢.
Jason: Oh.
麦琪:什么?
Maggie: What?
杰森:是的,我记得当时为和你单独出去,
Jason: Yeah, I remember how hard I had to work to get you alone on that
我拼命工作赚钱买了第一辆车.
first car of mine.
麦琪:我还记得当时你说的话."嘿,
Maggie: Well I still remember what you said."
马隆,想不想看我的激情飞车?"
Hey Malone, want to see my fuzzy dice?"
杰森:别笑,它当时有用.我对刚才的事很抱歉.
Jason: Don't laugh, it worked.I'm sorry about earlier.
麦琪:我也是.今晚我都错过了什么?
Maggie: Yeah, me too.So what kind of evening did I miss?
杰森:西贡小姐的前排座位,
Jason: Front row seats at Miss Saigon, a window table at the rainbow room,
彩虹餐厅靠窗的桌子,还有你非常喜欢的带花帽子的马,骑着它穿过中央公园.
and a buggy ride through central park with what horse in the little flowered hat that you love so much.
麦琪:啊,杰森.你真的计划了一个特别的夜晚.
Maggie: Ah, Jason, you really did want to make this a special night.
杰森:是的,我爱你麦琪.最近我很想你.
Jason: Yeah, I love you Maggie.Lately I miss you.
麦琪:我也想你.
Maggie: I miss you too.
杰森:好吧,我们现在在车里.没有孩子,什么也看不见.
Jason: Well, here we are in a parked car.No kids around, everything is dark.
麦琪:我要到前面去.
Maggie: I am coming back up front.
杰森:不,不.我有个更好的主意…哈
Jason: No, no.I got a better idea...yee haa.
麦琪:杰森,你和我在车后座上,我会想我爸爸用手电照我们.
Maggie: Jason, you and I in the back seat of a car, I half expect my father to shine his flashlight on us.
杰森:是的.
Jason: Yeah
警察:路通了,你们两个孩子快走,否则我就让你们的父母到警局去接你们.
Police Man: Roads clearing up, you kids beat it or I will have your parents
meet us at the station
麦琪:噢,杰森.很抱歉你错过了西贡小姐.
Maggie: Oh, Jason, I'm sorry you missed Miss Saigon.
杰森:看到了夫人我一样高兴.
Jason: I'm just glad I got to see Mrs.Seaver.
德怀特:嘿,你知道,我想这些帘子说不定真能管用.
Dwight: Hey, you know, I think this drape thing just might do it.
迈克:他就像活的妙语大全.
Mike: Your man's a walking punch line.
开萝尔:迈克,你为什么总和德怀特过不去?
Carol: Mike, why do you pick on Dwight so much?
迈克:噢,开萝尔,
Mike: Oh gee Carol, I don't know.
我也不知道.也许是因为他说话像小丑,
Maybe it's because he talks like a geek, he walks like a monkey,
走路像猴子,打扮有点像猩猩.
and he dresses like chimp.
事实上,我认为他是第四丑角.
In fact, I think he is the fourth stooge.
开萝尔:看,迈克.我是最先承认德怀特有点…
Carol: Look Mike, I'm the first to admit that Dwight's a little....
迈克:古怪?
Mike: Squirrelly?
开萝尔:不同.
Carol: Different.
迈克:你说对了.
Mike: Well you got that right.
开萝尔:我们得面对现实;那个盲目乐观的人在宇宙竞赛中会输给正常小姐.
Carol: Well let's face it;
Polly-Anna over there wouldn't win the Miss Normal of the universe contest.
迈克:这是什么意思?
Mike: What's that suppose to mean?
开萝尔:迈克,她吃草.
Carol: Mike, she grazes.
迈克:开萝尔,问题是,凯特爱我,我也爱她.你说的吃草我倒觉得很可爱.
Mike: Carol, the point is, Kate loves me and I love her.And for you information I think that grazing thing is kind of cute.
开萝尔:你对凯特的感觉,和我对德怀特的感觉一样.
Carol: The way you feel about Kate, that's how I feel about Dwight.
那是因为德怀特是我遇到的第一个欣赏并理解真实的我的人.
Well, it's just that Dwight is the first guy I've met who,
who appreciates and understands me for who I really am.
他对我来说非常重要,所以试着习惯吧.
He is my significant other, so get use to it.
迈克:这可要花点时间.
Mike: Could take a little while.
凯特:嘿,各位.
Kate: Hey everybody.
迈克:嘿,瞌睡虫!
Mike: Hey sleepy head!
凯特:这里真暖和,怎么了?
Kate: Why is it so warm in here, what happened?
迈克:噢,好吧,弯脚趾头…我是说德怀特,他的帘子主意救了我们.有时候他也挺聪明的.
Mike: Oh, well uh, curly toes...I mean Dwight, saved us with his drape idea.He can actually be pretty smart sometimes.
德怀特:没有你这事干不成,迈克.
Dwight: Couldn't have done it without you Mike.
凯特:不知道要多久才能来电.
Kate: I wonder how long tell the power comes on.
开萝尔:德怀特,为什么不来点音乐来帮我们度过这段时间?
Carol: Dwight, why don't you play some music for us to help us pass the time?
是的,他也会唱歌.
Yes, he sings too.
(唱歌)德怀特:你只要,你只要呼唤我的名字.
sing) Dwight: You just, you just call out my name and you know wherever I am,
(你知道无论我在哪.我都会跑过来,为了再次见到你.
That I'll come running, to see you again.
冬天,春天,夏天,或是秋天,
Winter, Spring, Summer, or Fall, all you got to do is call and I'll be there.
你需要做的就是呼唤,我就会出现.我会的.你的朋友.
I will.You got a friend.
迈克:我的天啊.
Mike: Oh my gosh.
开萝尔:来电了.噢!过来.
Carol: The black out's over.Yeah!Come here.
凯特:我想现在我们可以回家了.
Kate: Well I guess we can go home now.
开萝尔:是的,当然可以.但我还在品味刚才那首歌呢.
Carol: Yeah, sure can.But I was kind of enjoying that song though.
德怀特:是的,我也是.
Dwight: Yeah, me too.
迈克:好吧,我们唱完它.
Mike: Well hey, we can finish it.
迈克,德怀特,开萝尔,凯特:你只要,你只要呼唤我的名字.你知道无论我在哪.我都会跑过来,为了再次见到你.
Mike, Dwight, Carol, Kate: You just, you just call out my name and you know
wherever I am, I'll come running.To see you again
本:克莉丝,嗨,来电了.想上床睡觉吗?
克莉丝:不,我想和你在一起.
00:22:42,700
Ben: Chrissy, hi, the black out's over.Want me to put you to bed? Chrissy: No, I like it here with you.